譯者：微博@Emtee
我知道你醒着
I know you're awake.
看看他們
Look at them!
好好看看他們
Look at them very carefully,
他們的每一張臉
every single one of those faces.
都好好記住
And remember them dearly.
因爲明天你就要償還孽債
Because tomorrow you'll pay the devil's due.
明天你就將必死無疑
Tomorrow you'll head straight against the wall.
講得真棒啊
What a speech.
我好感動哦
I am very touched.
我叫你看照片
I said look at those photos!
你不知道爲了抓到你 我犧牲了什麽
You do not know what I sacrificed to finally catch you.
犧牲?
Sacrifice?
凡事皆有兩面 我的朋友
The door swings both ways, my friend.
朋友
My friend,
一切犧牲
all the sacrifice
全都是
is all for
徒勞
nothing.
拿好槍 你們現在全都自由了 好嗎
Take the guns. You're all free now. Okay?
拿著
Here.
謝謝 老大
Thank you, boss.
這才叫真傢伙
Now, this is a real gun.
這他媽什麽情况
What the fuck?
爆頭
譯者：微博@Emtee
兩個月後
抱歉 縫合得不是很好
Sorry, the sutures aren't that great.
是誰把你弄成這樣的
Who did this to you?
你又是誰
And who are you?
這樣就好了
That'll work.
抱歉 我幷不想這麽做
I'm sorry. I didn't want to do this.
打擾一下...
Excuse me...
小姐?
Miss?
見鬼 嘿 聽得到嗎
Shit, shit, shit. Hey Hey hey. Hello?
我在哪
Where am I ?
你在醫院 你在這有段時間了
You're in a hospital. You've been here for a while.
有親戚 家人嗎
Any relatives? Family?
你叫什麽
How about your name?
病人信息
伊什邁爾
伊什...
Ish...
伊什邁爾
Ishmael.
你的真名叫什麽
What about your real name?
馬上回來
Be right back.
一切都會好的
Everything will be all right.
記住是誰教你...
Remember who taught you ...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
伊什邁爾 現在你能起身了
Ishmael, you can get up now.
這是幹嘛
What's this for?
以防萬一而已
It's just a precaution.
謝謝 醫生
Thanks, doctor.
你可以叫我艾琳
You can call me Ailin.
總之 你先穿好衣服吧
Anyway, let's get you dressed.
怎麽了 醫生 累了?
What's wrong, doctor? Tired?
沒事 沒事 走吧
Nothing, nothing. Let's go.
你還記得什麽嗎
So, do you remember anything?
有些浮現的影像
I see shadows.
但感覺都不熟悉
But nothing feels familiar.
看
Look.
就那裏 那裏就是羅穆利發現你的地方
Just over there. That's where Romli found you.
他就是羅穆利
That's him right there, Romli.
你應該感謝的人是他
It's him you should be grateful to.
別這麽緊張
Don't be so tense.
我們去吃東西吧 我餓了
Now let's eat. I'm starving.
F5倉庫
他人呢
Where is he, huh?
耐心點 老大
Patience, boss.
不用多久的
It won't be long now.
- 行了 我走了 - 等下
- That's it, I'm out of here. - Hold on- -
耐心 是成功的根本
Patience. It's the essence of success.
請坐 坐吧
Please, sit. Sit down.
好了 我要開始吃了
Okay, then. I'm digging in.
很美味哦
Now, this is tasty.
想來點嗎
Want some?
李先生
Well, Mr. Lee.
我很尊重你 所以我就開門見山了
I respect you. So, I'll get straight to the point.
我要和你分道揚鑣
I'm cutting you loose.
什麽
Come again?
你的槍...都是中國垃圾
Your guns... Chinese junk.
還有這種...
And this...
都是不純的爛貨
Diluted crap.
我想和你做生意是因爲你的名聲
I wanted to do business with you because of your reputation.
李 大海之魔
Lee, the sea devil.
李 地獄之父
Lee, the father from hell.
瞧 擺脫你也會給我帶來一定名聲
You see, getting rid of you will give me a certain reputation, too.
我幹嘛帶這些人過來 就爲了跟你碰個面?
Why would I bring all these people just for a meeting with you?
所以你帶了這些人過來
So this is why you bring all these people
也帶了外面那些人過來
and the people outside.
我來搞定
I'll handle this.
見鬼
Oh, shit!
他...他...
He's... He's...
他不是我老大
He's not my boss.
中國垃圾 是吧
Chinese junk, huh?
這槍很好用啊
The gun is good.
不要 等下 老兄 我是說 老大
No, no, no. Wait, wait a second, bro- - I mean, boss.
等下
Wait, wait, wait...
我有消息 重要的消息
I got information. Important information.
給你
For you.
你逃走的那天
The day you escaped.
一名男子在海灘邊被發現 他被送進了醫院
They found a man by the beach, brought him to hospital.
我想說的是 據說他跟你的關係很近
My point is, I heard that he was very close to you.
現在我能走了嗎
Can I go now?
你是在耍我嗎 小子
You fucking with me, boy?
別打那裏 求你 了
Not there, please.
我沒胡說八道 消息都告訴你了
I'm not bullshitting. I gave you information.
求你了 我發誓
Please! I swear!
我向你保證 老大 我保證 我保證
I promise you, boss. I promise, I promise.
求你了 別殺我
Please. Please. Please, don't kill me.
- 求你了 給我一次機會 - 好的 一次機會
- Please, please. Give me a chance. - Okay. One chance.
好了 現在你可以走了
Okay. I'm leaving now.
見鬼
Fuck!
現在你可以去醫院查清楚了
Now you can go to the hospital and check it out.
見鬼
Fuck.
我他媽爲什麽非得等著
Why the fuck do I have to wait?
去叫醫生啊 把他帶過來
Just get the damn doctor. Bring him here.
治療我的耳朵 就沒你事了 就這麽簡單
Fix my ear, and you'll be done. It's that simple.
別這樣 先生 你會嚇到其他病人
Please, sir. You're scaring the other patients.
你長眼睛了吧 用你的眼睛看看我耳朵 看看
You got eyes, right? Use your eyes. Look at my ear. Look!
去叫醫生來治療我的耳朵
Call the doctor. And fix my fucking ear!
先生 別這樣 你得先填表
Sir, please, you still need to fill out the form.
搞什麽啊 你在逗我嗎
What the fuck? Are you kidding me?
- 你找死嗎 親愛的 - 先生 請冷靜
- Got a death wish, honey? - Sir, just calm down.
你說什麽
What did you say?
我說 請冷靜 先生
I said, calm down, sir.
- 我還是沒聽到  - 這是家醫院...
- Still can't hear. - This is a hospi- -
- 給我閉嘴 - 先生
- Shut the fuck up! - Sir!
請冷靜
Please calm down.
見鬼
Shit.
醫生 我痛死了
It hurts like hell, doc.
醫生
Doc.
據說一名快死的男子在海灘邊被人發現
I heard they found a dying guy down by the beach.
- 往上點  - 他被送了過來
- Tilt up. - And they brought him here.
我看過很多病人
I see a lot of patients.
所以你幷不否認海灘邊的那個人是在這裏
So, you're not denying it. The beach boy was here.
你在隱瞞什麽 對嗎
You're hiding something, aren't you?
沒錯...
Yeah. Sto- -
好了 現在你可以走了
We're done. You can go now.
- 真是快  - 謝謝
- About time. - Thank you.
醫生 你不能就這麽不管我
Can't just leave me high and dry, doctor.
他在哪
Where is he?
我要叫保安了
I'll call Security.
叫吧 去叫吧
Go ahead, go for it.
保安
Security!
Security.
看著我 我在這呢
Now look at me. Over here.
別自找沒趣
Quit the fucking games
告訴我他在哪
and tell me where he is.
除非你是想跟我找點樂子
Unless you want to play games with me.
搞什麽啊 放開我
What the fuck?! Let me go!
醫生 你沒事吧
Doc, are you all right?
伊什邁爾
Ishmael!
叫你逞能 混蛋
Take that, you fuck.
伊什邁爾 你還好嗎 伊什邁爾
Ishmael. Are you okay? Ishmael.
伊什邁爾 你還好嗎
Ishmael, are you okay?
伊什邁爾
Ishmael.
- 伊什邁爾 - 怎麽了
- Ishmael. - Yes?
你認得那個人嗎
Did you recognize that guy?
你之前的反應讓我很擔心
Your reaction earlier had me worried.
你待在這裏可能會有危險
It could be dangerous for you to stay here.
或許你該跟我去雅加達
Maybe it's better for you to come with me to Jakarta?
雅加達?
Jakarta?
我給你看樣東西
I'll show you something.
我們發現你的頭骨裏有异物
We found foreign particles in your skull,
就在海馬區旁邊 我們沒法取出它們
right by the hippocampus area, and we couldn't extract them.
所以我想要你跟我去雅加達
That's why I want you to come with me to Jakarta.
那邊的設施更好 可以把它們從你頭部去除
They have better facilities to remove them from your head.
伊什邁爾
Ishmael?
在
Yes.
你怎麽說
What say you?
如果我不是好人呢 你還會在我身邊嗎
What if I'm not a good person? Would you still be there for me?
伊什邁爾 你不是壞人
Ishmael, you're not a bad person.
所以我得搞清楚我是誰
That's why I need to find out who I am.
我保證 無論發生什麽...我們都會再次相見
I promise, whatever happens... we will meet again.
給 拿著
Here. Take it.
上面只有一個號碼
There's only one number on it.
你搞清楚之後
After you find yourself,
去雅加達找我
look me up in Jakarta.
你會體驗到真正的堵車
Bet you've never experienced a real traffic jam before.
如果我醫術有成了
And if I become a successful doctor,
別指望我會免費檢查
don't expect free checkups.
別...
Don't...
好啦 放鬆
Relax. Take it easy.
我不會拋弃你
I won't abandon you.
再跟你說下 這是你的X光片
I'll show you again. These are your x-rays.
你頭部的异物...
The particles went into your head...
伊什邁爾
Ishmael.
又想起什麽了? 伊什邁爾
Another episode? Ishmael?
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
抱歉
Sorry.
我沒事 我很好
It's nothing. I'm okay.
去渡囗 準備開船了
Going to the ferry station, ready for departure.
到我的班次了
That's my ride.
該死
Fuck!
謝謝 先生 回頭見
Thank you, sir. See you later.
這邊 看這邊 孩子
Over here. Here, kid!
怎麽那麽難過啊
Why so sad?
過來
Get over here.
前面是什麽情况
What's going on here?
怎麽了
What's the matter?
他在哪
Where is he?
阿布迪
Abdi?
他在哪
Where is he?!
你好
Hello?
艾琳?
Ailin?
- 伊什邁爾 伊什邁爾  - 艾琳?艾琳?
- Ishmael. Ishmael. - Ailin? Ailin?
- 他們槍殺了司機  - 你在哪
- They shot the driver. - Where are you?!
媽媽
Mommy.
醒醒 媽媽
Wake up, Mommy.
小姑娘
Little girl.
別難過
Don't be sad.
媽媽和神在一起了
Mommy is with God now.
等下 等下 等下
Wait, wait, wait...
阿布迪在哪
Where's Abdi?
阿布迪是誰
Abdi? Who?
等等 你醫院的那個朋友
Wait, wait, wait. Your friend from the hospital.
他不在這裏 他沒走
He isn't here. He never left.
怎麽搞的 踩踏板試試
What is it now? Try hitting the pedals.
嘿 等下 該死的 你下車去哪 等等啊
Hey, hey, hey. Wait, damn it. Where are you off to? Wait a sec.
艾琳
Ailin!
Ailin.
艾琳
該死 好難聞
Damn. Smells like shit.
他說燒了這輛巴士
Burn the bus, he said.
好臭
It stinks!
我可不想上去
Sucks to be you.
把汽油給我
Pass me the gasoline!
就來 先剁碎他們 那樣更容易燒
It's coming. Chop them up first so they'll burn easier.
- - 你他媽是誰 - 我在找一個朋友
- Who the fuck are you? - I'm just looking for a friend.
- 是嗎 - 是的
- Really? - Yes.
這是你朋友嗎
Is this your friend?
見鬼
Shit.
什麽情况
What the fuck?!
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
你他媽去死吧 去死吧
Go fucking die! Go die!
去你媽的
Fuck you!
先生
Sir!
挺住 先生
Hang in there, sir.
冷靜 孩子 放鬆
Relax, kid. Easy now.
先生 挺住啊
Please, sir. Sir! Just hang in there.
先生
Sir!
抓住他
Get him.
該死
Damn.
這他媽是什麽地方
What the fuck is this place?
該死
Damn.
這是你們的藏匿所?
So, this is your hideout?
真不錯啊 但爲什麽把小孩子也帶來了
Pretty cool. But why bring the little kid, too?
她毫無用處 帶來幹嘛
She's useless! What's the point?
知道你們的老闆 李 怎麽跟我說的嗎
You know what your boss, Lee, told me?
把他要的那個傢伙帶來就...
Just bring the guy that he asked- -
你廢話太多了
You talk too much.
那個小女孩在哪
Where's the little girl?!
警察局
嘿
Hey.
注意點
Please focus.
羅穆利 本地居民
Romli, local resident.
他跟你什麽關係
He your relation?
朋友
A friend.
好的 朋友
Okay, a friend.
告訴我 發生了什麽事
Now, tell me, what happened?
我朋友之前在巴士上 她和他們在一塊兒
My friend was in the bus. She was with them.
你是說那些死了的人?
Those dead people, you mean?
是的 長官 但我沒找到她
Yes, sir. But I didn't find her.
她是個來自雅加達的醫生 叫艾琳
She's a doctor from Jakarta, her name's Ailin.
- 艾琳 - 是的
- Ailin. - Yeah.
那麽 是誰殺了那些人呢
So, who killed those people then?
來 告訴我
Go on, tell me.
長官 你一定要相信我
Sir, you have to believe me.
我必須找到我的朋友 我必須找到艾琳
I have to find my friend. I have to find Ailin.
出去
Out.
現在只有我們了
It's... just us now.
- 看見沒 - 是啊
- See? - Yes.
別跟我胡扯
Stop bullshitting me.
不然我把你關進監獄
Or else I'll throw you in the fucking brig.
你知道我底細就動手啊
If you know anything about me, then go right ahead!
隨你怎麽樣
Do whatever you want!
但我沒這個時間
But I don't have time for this.
嘿 冷靜 冷靜 別激動
Hey. Easy, easy. Relax.
既然你堅持你是無辜的
Since you insist on being innocent...
好 看看這個吧
Okay, look at this.
你認得他嗎 你認識他嗎
Do you recognize him? You know him?
translated by weibo -
e
t
m
E
我來講個故事 幫你恢復下記憶
Let me refresh your memory with a story.
你會覺得這個故事聽起來很熟悉
This story might sound familiar to you.
伊什邁爾
Ishmael.
曾經有一個傳聞...
There was once a rumor...
是關于一個神秘的年輕男子
about a mysterious young man.
他每次現身
Every time he appears,
都會留下一片血流成河的大屠殺場景
he leaves a scene of massacre that turns the whole beach blood red.
孩子中 不超過6歲或10歲的 也都會不見踪影
Children, none older than 6 or 10, would disappear as well.
你想知道哪些孩子都怎麽樣了嗎
Do you want to know what happened to those children?
那些孩子長大了
Those children grew up.
他們被養育成了走私犯...
They were bred to become smugglers...
搶劫犯...
plunderers...
和殺手
and killers.
想像一下
Imagine that.
這些小鬼掌控著這座島
These brats have a stranglehold on this island.
譯者 微博@Emtee
一群王八蛋
Sons of bitches.
他們每個人都願意...
Everyone of them willing to die...
爲那個神秘的
for their mysterious
恐怖大師而死
terrorist master.
人們不禁好奇
Now, one has to wonder.
這個人是誰
Who is this person?
即便在罪犯之中 他也是個可怕的人物
Even amongst criminals, he's a terrifying figure.
少數存活的人講到這些事時
Few who live to tell the tale...
將他簡單地稱爲 李
refer to him simply as "Lee."
這跟我有什麽關係
What's it got to do with me?
兩個月前...
Two months ago...
我們走了大運
we hit the jackpot.
我們出乎意料地
Right out of the blue,
發現李
we found Lee,
就坐在露天場所
sitting out in the open.
沒有武裝 不受保護
Unarmed. Unguarded.
想像一下
Imagine that.
這太瘋狂了
Crazy.
但你瞧 伊什邁爾
But you see, Ishmael.
- 更瘋狂的是... - 你還沒回答我的問題
- It gets even crazier- - - You haven't answered my question.
現在你怎麽說 人渣
What do you say now, scum?
聽著 我真的不知道...
Listen, I really don't know- -
把燈打開
Turn the lights back on!
這他媽是怎麽回事
What the fuck is going on?
你是誰
Who are you?
我是...
I am...
走 上吧
Come on, let's go.
出口
去開電源
Turn the power back on.
阿布迪...
Abdi...
三
Three.
四
Four.
躲起來?你他媽人呢
Hiding? Where the fuck are you?
我還想玩玩呢
I still wanna play.
該死 真會玩...
Ah, fuck. Not bad...
老兄
Bro.
嘿 老兄
Hey, bro.
想知道我對你的婊子做了什麽嗎
Wanna know what I did to that bitch of yours?
去你他媽的
Fuck you!
你就是那個救了阿布迪的人?
So, you're the one? Abdi's savior.
他是你什麽人?
What is he to you?
阿布迪是個好名字
A good name, Abdi.
本應該代表忠誠
It's supposed to mean loyalty.
你是誰
Who are you?
別殺他
Don't kill him.
告訴他 他女人在我們手上
Tell him we got his woman.
泰喬?
Tejo?
我還在這裏
I'm still here.
我會過來的
And I'll be coming.
你還記得你的父親吧 阿布迪
You still remember your father, right, Abdi?
李
Lee.
好孩子
That's my boy.
艾琳
Ailin!
- 伊什邁爾  - 艾琳
- Ishmael. - Ailin!
- 李 放開她 - 你聽到了嗎
- Lee! Let her go! - You hear that?
發送位置
你應該刺這裏
You should have stuck here.
我當你是醫生呢
I thought you were a doctor.
現在你記起來了嗎
Do you remember it now?
那個鬼地方的所有回憶
All the memories from that fucking place?
你記起來了 對嗎 他把我們扔進那個井裏
You remember, right? He threw us into that well.
就這樣把人渣和他隔離
It's what separates him from other scum.
他把我們從我們父母身邊奪走
He took us from our parents.
他教我們如何生存 如何殺人
He taught us how to survive and how to kill.
好幾天 甚至好幾周 都沒有食物 沒有水
Days, even weeks, without food. Without water.
然而...正是這種苦難把我們變成了兄弟
Yet... it's that very suffering that turned us into brothers.
但最後幷非如此
That's not how it ends though.
是啊
Yeah.
一瓶水能把絕望的孩子變成殺人犯
A bottle of water could turn desperate kids into murderers.eetme#obiewybdetalsnart
正因此 他才被稱爲地獄之父
Hence, the father from hell.
你對這一切都很清楚 爲什麽還爲他賣命
If you know all about it, why are you still on his side?
每個人都必須選擇立場 追隨那個混蛋是我的命運
Everyone has to choose a side. Following that fucker is my fate.
你的生命有了新的延續 你爲什麽來這裏
You have a new lease on life. Why are you here?
離開吧 我饒你一命
Back off and I'll let you live.
貝西
BESI ...
我現在不能離開
I can't back off now.
就爲了那個醫生?
All this for the doctor?
就像你說的 每個人都必須選擇立場
Like you said, everyone has to choose a side.
我可不像泰喬和塔諾那麽容易對付
This won't be as easy as Tejo or Tano.
好樣的 阿布迪
Well done, Abdi.
絕殺時刻到了
Now comes the final drill.
阿布迪...
Abdi...
貝西一直是向著你的
Besi was always on your side.
你就這麽回報他嗎
And this is how you repay him?
你是在讓我們四分五裂 阿布迪
You're tearing us apart, Abdi!
記得我嗎 阿布迪
Remember me, Abdi?
還是說我該叫你伊什邁爾
Or should I call you Ishmael?
艾琳在哪
Where's Ailin?
帶我去她那裏
Take me to her.
我不知道哪個讓我更難過
I don't know which makes me sadder,
是看見你殺死你自己的人...
watching you killing your own...
還是看見你現在可悲的樣子
or seeing the sorry state you're in now.
你知道我們曾有多親近嗎
Do you know how close we were?
爲什麽要變呢 阿布迪
Why does it have to change, Abdi?
大概是因爲你往我頭裏射了發子彈
Probably because you put a bullet in my head.
你背叛了父親 對吧
You betrayed father, right?
如果你要我選擇...
If you ask me to choose...
你知道我會選誰
you know whom I would choose.
麗卡...
Rika...
這一切已經太久了 我不想再殺人
this has been going for far too long. I don't wanna kill anymore.
這一切都是爲了她 對嗎
So, it's all about her, right?
別把艾琳扯進來
Leave Ailin out of this.
既然你那麽想要她...
Since you want her that bad...
麗卡
Rika!
Rika.
够了 麗卡
That's enough, Rika.
麗卡
Rika.
够了
That's enough.
記得這地方嗎 我們小時候在這裏訓練
Remember this place? We trained here as kids.
即使那時 我也總是很欣賞你 阿布迪
Even then, I always admired you, Abdi.
那是最快樂的時光
Those were the happiest moments.
聽我說
Listen to me.
你能離開李
You can get away from Lee.
你能選擇自由
You have the choice to be free.
麗卡
Rika.
麗卡 別...
Rika, no...
現在...
Now...
我們扯平了
we're even.
麗卡
Rika.
我什麽都記起來了
I remember everything.
你把我們養育成惡狼
You raised us to be wolves.
我們只擅長殺戮
All we were good for was killing.
這是爲了讓你們都變得更强
It was meant to make you all stronger.
或許吧
Maybe so.
但現在一切都已明瞭
But it's all apparent now.
你不是傳奇 也不是父親
You're neither a legend, nor a father.
不自由 毋寧死
只是個脅迫小孩的老頭
Just an old man who bullies little kids.
最終你犯了個錯誤
In the end you made a mistake.
好吧
Ok.
你就先回家吧
Why don't you just come home?
我們會解決這問題的
We'll settle this.
我已經到了
I'm already here.
快 快
Hurry! Hurry!
去角落躲好
Go hide in the corner.
鑰匙呢
Where's the key?
起來
Get up.
快 起來
Come on, get up.
轉身
Turn around.
- 爲什麽 - 轉身啊
- Why? - I said, turn around!
別動
Stay still!
該死的婊子
Fucking bitch!
你們兩個都死定了
You're both dead!
婊子 你連開槍都不會
Bitch! You can't even shoot.
不要 等下啊 放下槍
No, wait! Drop it!
我們趕緊跑吧
Let's get the hell out.
走吧 快走
Let's go. Let's go.
38區
這邊
This way.
怎麽回事
What was that?
艾琳
Ailin.
是我
It's me.
艾琳
Ailin?
艾琳 你沒事吧
Ailin, are you all right?
艾琳...
Ailin...
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
- 你傷得重嗎 - 閉嘴
- Are you hurt bad? - Shut up!
艾琳 請冷靜下
Ailin, please calm down.
走開 我們要出去
Get out of the way! We're leaving.
沒錯 我們要出去
Yes, we will leave.
你和他們是一夥的
You're one of them.
你跟他們完全一樣
You are exactly like them!
沒錯
Yes.
你說得沒錯
You're right.
我爲了擺脫他們而做的一切
Everything that I've done to get away from them...
讓我走到了這一天 這一刻
brought me to this day, this very second.
你之前救了我
You saved me before.
我要你再救我一次
I need you to save me one more time.
伊什邁爾...
Ishmael...
醒醒 醒醒
Wake up! Wake up!
你看那邊幹嘛 看著我啊
Why you look over there? Look at me.
我叫你看著我
I said look at me!
我是你父親
I am your father!
你...
You...
你就是條不懂服從二字的狗
You're just a fucking dog who does not know the word "obey".
麗卡在哪
Where's Rika?
她死了嗎
Is she dead?
你殺了她?
You killed her?
她很久以前就死了
She died a long time ago.
你把她從井裏拉出去的那一刻 她就死了
From the moment you pulled her out of that well.
他們都在被你抓住時就死了
All of them died when you first laid your hands on them.
爲什麽 這一切是爲什麽 爲什麽啊
Why? Why all this? What for?
你是我的兒子 阿布迪 我的兒子
You are my son, Abdi! My son!
阿布迪?
Abdi?
因爲你每次都用那個名字稱呼我
For every time you call me by that name.
那就動手吧
So be it, then.
我的兒子
My son...
你知道嗎
You know?
養育你是我最大的錯誤
Raising you was my greatest mistake
我不得不爲之付出代價
and I have to pay for it.
而你也一樣
And so will you.
阿布迪
Abdi.
李
Lee!
伊什邁爾
Ishmael.
別閉上眼睛 伊什邁爾
Don't close your eyes, Ishmael.
伊什邁爾 看著我
Ishmael. Just look at me.
伊什邁爾 伊什邁爾
Ishmael. Ishmael.
不要離開我
Don't leave me.
求你了 伊什邁爾
Please ... Ishmael.
這感覺好熟悉
This feels familiar.
覺得雅加達怎麽樣
So, how's Jakarta?
至少這次的床舒服多了吧
At least the bed's better this time.
我會等到你出院
Just wait until you get out.
你還什麽都沒體驗過呢
You've experienced nothing yet.
所以 這次...
So, please...
請別讓我又等兩個月
Don't make me wait another two months this time.
好嗎
Okay?
病人診斷
名字 阿布迪
你應該寫...
You should write...
伊什邁爾
Ishmael.
譯者：微博@Emtee
譯者:微博@Emtee